Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.20
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Dick Thornburgh Papers, Series XX. Audio Recordings
1976-1993
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Thornburgh, Dick
AIS.1998.30.20
547 items
The Dick Thornburgh audio collection, consists of 547 audio tapes, with 9 hours from 31 items online here. The content of the collection of tapes is extensive and highly varied, from the conflicts and excitement of campaigns to press conferences and speeches related to the nuclear accident at Three Mile Island (TMI). There are numerous press interviews with particularly challenging questions and answers regarding virtually all the significant issues and accomplishments of Thornburgh's career. The earliest audio is the swearing in ceremony of Lieutenant Governor Scranton in January 1979, and the latest a 1993 BBC interview regarding Thornburgh's year as Under-Secretary-General of the United Nations. Digital reproductions of portions of the collection are available online.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dick Thornburgh, February 27, 1998.
Previous Citation
Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932-, AIS.1998.30, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Politics; Women; United States -- Politics and government -- 20th century; Pennsylvania -- Politics and government -- 1951-; Political campaigns -- Pennsylvania; Social action; Environment; Personal papers; Government; Thornburgh, Dick; Pennsylvania. Governor (1979-1987: Thornburgh); Three Mile Island Nuclear Power Plant (Pa.); United States. Attorney-General; United States. Congress. Senate -- Elections; Pennsylvania. Governor -- Elections; Thornburgh, Ginny (Judson)
- Audio, 1976-1993; XX.
  Scope and Contents note
  Thornburgh's press officers and staff throughout his career frequently used audio tapes as an appropriate way to document informal remarks and press conferences in particular, but the collection also includes tapes of more formal ceremonies and events. The audios are from the periods when Thornburgh served as Governor of Pennsylvania, Attorney General of the United States, campaigns for Governor and U.S. Senate, and into his ongoing career. The Thornburgh collection includes more than 500 such tapes. In particular 9 hours from 31 items have been digitized and are available to here online.
  The content of the collection of tapes is extensive and highly varied, from the conflicts and excitement of campaigns to some incredible press conferences and speeches related to the nuclear accident at Three Mile Island (TMI). There are numerous press interviews with particularly challenging questions and answers regarding virtually all the significant issues and accomplishments of Thornburgh's career, and both formal speeches and informal remarks at events. Perhaps surprisingly, these audios are extremely interesting even in our current world focused more on visual and video presentations.
  The audios that have been digitized for the website are as varied as the collection as a whole. The earliest is the swearing in ceremony of Lieutenant Governor Scranton in January, 1979, and the latest a 1993 BBC interview regarding Thornburgh's year spent as Under-Secretary-General of the United Nations. Much of the content of the audios is unavailable in other formats, thus particularly of interest. The Three Mile Island news conference with Harold Denton of the NRC on March 31, 1979 and the following day's press conference with President Carter are notable. There are presentations newly established by Thornburgh during his years as Governor such as the Distinguished Art Award to Actor Jimmy Stewart and the Distinguished Service Medal to General Matthew B. Ridgeway. Both of these are particularly compelling. There is also a brief and somewhat difficult to hear welcome to Pope John Paul II by Governor Thornburgh on the tarmac at Philadelphia airport, with the Pope's response. Although Ginny Thornburgh worked to the benefit of the Commonwealth every day during the Governor's two terms in office we have but one speech of hers which was given on Mother's Day to the students at Valley Forge Military Academy.
  Audios of Dick Thornburgh cover most all major topics with which he grappled and was concerned. Just for example, there are speeches and remarks about Three Mile Island and its long-ranging aftermath, national energy concerns, education and welfare reform, job creation, balanced budgets, Rule of Law, civil justice reform, the role of the United Nations, judicial appointments, drug trafficking, the savings and loan scandals, and disability law. The press conference following Thornburgh's gubernatorial trip to Japan and China is very informative and his remarks in Moscow on the occasion of the historic first visit of an Attorney General to the Soviet Union are notable. As a change of pace the musical tourism campaign ads "You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania," and the Governor's performance at the outrageous annual press Gridiron event, 1984, are enjoyable.
  - Early Legal Career, 1970s; 1.
    - Eyewitness News regarding Tony Grosso convicted numbers racketeer, May 29, 1976 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 001)
    - KDKA-TV Eyewitness News "Newsmakers", June 5, 1977 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 002)
    - 1250 WTAE with Dick Thornburgh & Bob Kopler, July 24, 1977 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 003)
    - National Governor's Conference, August 25, 1977 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 004)
  - Campaign for Governor, 1978; 2.
    - Harrisburg Reports regarding Marston, Cigarette Smuggling, Begler Hearings, and Flaherty and Kline Running for Governor, January 27, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 005)
    - Butera Commercial, Philadelphia Radio, February 11, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 006)
    - 11 pm News Report regarding Marston Announcements, Philadelphia, March 13, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 007)
    - Speech to ARCO Employees in Philadelphia, March 15, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 008)
    - Thornburgh-Punxsutawney, September 17, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 009)
    - Black Republican Meeting, September 30, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 010)
    - Pete Flaherty Campaign Ad, October 15, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 011)
    - Ray Fox Show: Lieutenant Gubernatorial Candidates Scranton and Casey's Only Gubernatorial Debate, October 28, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 012)
    - Annual Press Gridiron Show, September, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 013)
    - Pittsburgh Post Gazette Editorial Board regarding Grosso issue and "dirty tricks", November 1, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 014)
    - 1978 Campaign Press conference regarding Tony Grosso and dirty tricks, November 4, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 015)
    - KQV News regarding Grosso News Conference, November 4, 1978 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 016)
    - Inaugural Ceremony of Governor, January 18, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 017)
    - Lieutenant Governor Scranton's Inaugural Ceremony [online], January 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 018)
  - Governor, 1979-1987; 3.
    - Contract signing; Cressona Aluminum with Alcoa, January 30, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 019)
    - "Highway Maintenance" Press conference, Harrisburg, February 5, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 020)
    - Allegheny County Republican Lincoln Day Dinner and Press Conference, Pittsburgh, February 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 021)
    - National Governors Association radio interviews, Washington, D.C., February 27, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 022)
    - University of Pennsylvania radio interviews, Philadelphia, February 28, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 023)
    - Swearing-in ceremony: PA State Police Commissioner Daniel F. Dunn, Harrisburg, March 1, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 024)
    - Pennsylvania Cross of Valor presented to Sgt. Kenneth L. Krause, Harrisburg, March 5, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 025)
    - Budget Address, Harrisburg, March 7, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 026)
    - Budget Press Briefing and Questions and Answers, Harrisburg, March 7, 1979; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 027 028)
    - Press conference, Johnstown: flood relief grants, March 10, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 029)
    - Speech: Bill Davis, Secretary of Community Affairs, Greensburg, March 15, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 030)
    - Governor's Swearing-in Ceremony for Seven Cabinet members, March 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 031)
    - Press conference, Harrisburg: cutting work force and auto fleet, March 22, 1979; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 032 033)
    - Swearing-in Ceremony for Gorham Black, Secretary of Aging, Camp Hill, PA, March 23, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 034)
    - Press announcement regarding federal and state cigarette smuggling, Harrisburg, April 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 035)
    - WTAE-TV "Close Up" interview with Governor Thornburgh regarding events and details of Three Mile Island (TMI) nuclear accident, Pittsburgh [online], April 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 036A)
    - Speech to the University of Pittsburgh Engineering Alumni Program regarding issues following the nuclear accident at Three Mile Island (TMI), Pittsburgh [online], April 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 036B)
    - Speech to the Pennsylvania Manufacturers Association, Philadelphia, April 24, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 037)
    - Speech to the Lancaster Association of Commerce and Industry, Lancaster, April 24, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 038)
    - Press conference with PA Township Supervisors, Hershey; "Another Voice", Hershey, April 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 039)
    - Press conference, Hershey and American Presspaper Publishers Association Press Conference on Emergencies, NYC, April 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 040)
    - American Newspaper Publishers Association Convention Panel, NYC; Barbara Walters; Speech regarding International Trade, Hershey, April 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 041)
    - Friends of Independence National Historic Park, WFLN-AM/FM Radio, April 27, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 042)
    - "Saratoga" Press Conference, Philadelphia Naval Shipyards and WTAF-TV "Pressprobe", May 1, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 043)
    - Pennsylvania Farm Show Press Conference, Harrisburg, May 3, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 044)
    - PA Economy League Board of Directors Meeting, Hershey, May 4, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 045)
    - Shippensburg State College Commencement, Shippensburg, PA, May 5, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 046)
    - Speech to the Governor's Highway Safety Conference Luncheon, Camp Hill, May 8, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 047)
    - Department of Revenue's Division of Motor Vehicles Tax Press Conference, Harrisburg, May 9, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 048)
    - Speech to West Branch Manufacturer's Association, Williamsport, May 9, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 049)
    - Speech to PA Chamber of Commerce, Hershey, May 10, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 050)
    - G.O.P. Fundraiser Speech and Press Conference, Lebanon, PA, May 11, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 051)
    - Speeches to the County Maintenance Managers, Mechanicsburg; PA Federation of Woman's Clubs, Hershey; American Society for Public Administration, Hershey, May 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 052)
    - Speech to the Pennsylvania Publishers Association, State College, May 18, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 053)
    - Speeches to the PA State Education Association, Pittsburgh, and to the PA Associated Press Broadcasters Association, Lancaster, May 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 054)
    - PA Associated Press Broadcasters Association Press Conference, Lancaster, May 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 055)
    - Greater Harrisburg Arts Festival Awards Ceremony, Harrisburg, May 22, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 056)
    - Speech to the Greater Philadelphia Cultural Alliance, Philadelphia, May 23, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 057)
    - Temple University Commencement, Philadelphia, May 24, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 058)
    - WNEP-TV "Live" Interview regarding the Budget, Wilkes-Barre, and Speech to the Greater Wilkes-Barre Chamber of Commerce, May 29, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 059)
    - Speech to the PA Automotive Association Convention, Lancaster, May 31, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 060)
    - WPVI-TV "Live" Interview, Philadelphia and Metropolitan Christian Council of Philadelphia, June 1, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 061)
    - Milton Hershey School Commencement, Hershey, June 4, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 062)
    - Speech to the AFL-CIO, Philadelphia, June 4, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 063)
    - Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, June 7, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 064)
    - Army War College Commencement, Carlisle, June 11, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 065)
    - Speech to the Opportunities Industrialization Centers, Washington DC, June 12, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 066)
    - Speech and Press Conference to the Annual Meeting of the PA American Automotive Association Federation, Pittsburgh, June 15, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 067)
    - Speech to the Council on Welfare Fraud, Harrisburg, June 18, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 068)
    - Speech to the PA Association of Mutual Insurance Companies, Camp Hill, June 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 069)
    - Press Conference with Governor Byrne of NJ regarding Three Mile Island (TMI), Harrisburg, June 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 070)
    - Gasoline Supply Press Conference, Harrisburg, June 21, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 071)
    - Speech/Q&A to the Associated Press Management Editors Association Luncheon, West Haven, PA, June 22, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 072)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony and Press Conference for the Allegheny Valley Expressway, Tarentum and the Allegheny Expressway Luncheon, New Kensington, June 23, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 073)
    - PA State Association of Boroughs Conference, Hershey, June 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 074)
    - Press Conference; gasoline-odd/even days, Harrisburg, June 27, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 075)
    - Speech to the 35th Biennial Convention of The Grand Lodge of PA Order of Sons of Italy in America Dinner, Lancaster, June 29, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 076)
    - Budget Settlement Press Conference, Harrisburg, July 5, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 077)
    - Speech to the Greater Johnstown Chamber of Commerce, Johnstown, July 12, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 078)
    - Speech at the Abex Corporation Check Presentation, Johnstown, July 12, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 079)
    - WJAC-TV "Viewpoint", H.B 780 Signing, and Speech to the Rehabilitation Center, Johnstown, July 12, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 080)
    - Philadelphia Council of Neighborhood Organizations Meeting, Philadelphia; Sewerage Grant Transfer Bill Signing and Press Conference; US Environmental Protection Agency, Philadelphia; and KYW-TV 6 with Governor DuPont of DE, Philadelphia, July 18, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 081)
    - Bradford Centennial Luncheon, July 24, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 082)
    - Press Conference, Erie, July 24, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 083)
    - Press Conference, Indiana, PA, August 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 084)
    - Speech to the Agricultural Progress Days and GOP Fundraiser Press Conference, Centre County, August 23, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 085)
    - "I Love Erie Day" Press Conference and WICU-TV "Focus-12", Erie, August 24, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 086)
    - Speech to the Bradford Coal Company, State College and Keynote Address to the PA Coal Mining Association Dinner, State College, August 29, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 087)
    - Speech at the Expo '79 International Year of the Child, Hershey and Speech to the PA Occupational Safety and Health Conference, Harrisburg, September 5, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 088)
    - Charles F. Scarlata Fundraiser Press Conference, Pittsburgh, September 6, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 089)
    - PA Department of Transportation Inspector General Press Conference, Harrisburg and Speech at the International Year of the Child-Expo 79, Hershey, September 17, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 090)
    - Annual Gridiron Show, September 17, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 091)
    - Governor Monologue Gridiron Program, Harrisburg, September 17, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 092)
    - Speeches to the Graduate Hospital, Philadelphia and to the Union League of Philadelphia, September 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 093)
    - Speech to the Philadelphia Distinguished Republicans Dinner, Philadelphia, September 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 094)
    - Legislative Priorities Press Briefing, Harrisburg, October 2, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 095)
    - Governor and Pope John Paul II greeting each other at airport in Philadelphia [online], October 3, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 096)
    - Speech to PA Council on Aging, Philadelphia, October 3, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 097)
    - Speech to the PA Society of Association Executives, Hershey, October 5, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 098)
    - WIP Radio: "The Decision Makers" Interview, October 7, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 099)
    - Speech to the PA Council of Republican Women, Harrisburg, October 8, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 100)
    - Speech to the Haverford Senior High School, Haverford, October 10, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 101)
    - Williamsport Court House Press Conference: coal gasification, October 11, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 102)
    - Speeches to Bloomsburg State College, Bloomsburg and the Can Do, Inc. Groundbreaking Ceremony, Hazelton, October 11, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 103)
    - West End Bridge By-Pass Press Conference, Pittsburgh and Scarlata Headquarters Press Conference, Pittsburgh, October 12, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 104)
    - "Pennsylvania Day" Reception and Press Conference, Harrisburg and the PA Tax Committee, Harrisburg, October 17, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 105)
    - Mainline Chamber of Commerce, October 25, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 107)
    - Bucks County Fundraising, October 26 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 108)
    - Carmichael Area Schools, November 8, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 109)
    - Ethics Code Press Conference, Harrisburg, November 15, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 110)
    - GPU Energy Metropolitan Edison Meeting, Harrisburg, November 16, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 111)
    - "Education - The State Priority," Speech to the PA Dept. of Education's Education Conference, Hershey and "How to Handle the Psychology Resulting from a Nuclear Emergency," Speech to the Republican Governor's Association, Austin, TX, November 16, 1979 and November 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 112)
    - Steel Industry Shutdowns Press Conference, Harrisburg, December 6, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 113)
    - National Union of Hospital and Health, December 8, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 114)
    - De-briefing on Soviet Jewry following Trip to Soviet Union, Harrisburg, December 11, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 115)
    - Governor's First Town Meeting, Lancaster, PA, December 18, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 116)
    - Thornburgh's First Year in Office Interview, Harrisburg and Speech at the "God Bless America Day" Rally, Harrisburg, December 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 117)
    - PPTN: Thornburgh's First Year in Office Interview, Harrisburg [online], December 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 118)
    - Gannon College, Gannon Press Avail, December 19, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 119)
    - Press conference with Philadelphia Mayor-Elect Bill Green, Harrisburg, December 20, 1979 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 120)
    - Christmas Program, Capital, December 20 (Box 1603, Cassette DTA 121)
    - 1980 PA Farm Show Opening, Harrisburg, January 6, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 122)
    - "Bethlehem Review" Interview, Harrisburg, January 8, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 123)
    - Ethnic Committee Ceremonies, Harrisburg, January 10, 1980; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 124 125)
    - UPI: Thornburgh's First Year in Office Interview, Harrisburg, January 16, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 126)
    - First year in Office Interview with Sandy Starobin, Harrisburg, January 16, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 127)
    - Center Daily Times Interview, Harrisburg, January 21, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 128)
    - Thornburgh's Narration of Aaron Copeland's "A Lincoln Portrait" at the Harrisburg Symphony, Harrisburg, January 22, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 129)
    - Speech to the Coal Conference, Hershey, January 23, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 130)
    - Speech to the Harrisburg Redevelopment Authority for Harrisburg Railway Station, Harrisburg, January 25, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 131)
    - Speech at the Republican Legislative Task Force Breakfast, West Virginia, January 29, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 132)
    - Speech to the Elizabethtown Chamber of Commerce, Elizabethtown, January 30, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 133)
    - Budget Message to the Joint Session of the General Assembly, Harrisburg, February 5, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 134)
    - Budget Press Conference, Harrisburg, February 6, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 135)
    - O' Bannon & Scanlon Budget Press Conference, February 7, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 136)
    - League of Women Voters of Pennsylvania, 60th Anniversary, Harrisburg, February 13, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 137)
    - Hazardous and Toxic Waste Press Conference, February 14, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 138)
    - Founder's Day at Lebanon Valley College, Annville, February 19, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 139)
    - Cigna, February 21, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 140)
    - Japan/China Trip: Governor's comments in Press Conference, Harrisburg [online], March 19, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 141)
    - Remarks to the Marchers for the American Hostages in Iran, Harrisburg, March 24, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 142)
    - Tourism Campaign Press Conference, Hershey, March 25, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 143)
    - H.B 640 Divorce Reform Bill Signing, Harrisburg, April 2, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 144)
    - "You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania," musical tourism ads [online], April 2, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 145)
    - Chester County Meeting: Chester, PA, April 3, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 146)
    - Convocation Address at the 75th Anniversary of Villanova's College of Engineering, Villanova and WCAU-TV, Philadelphia, April 15, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 147)
    - Speech at the PA Recognition Day Ceremony Honoring the First Women Graduates from Service Academies, Harrisburg, April 18, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 148)
    - "The Pennsylvanian" (Amtrak Passenger Train) Press Conferences in Harrisburg, Lewistown, Huntingdon, Tyrone, Altoona, Johnstown, Latrobe, Greensburg, and Pittsburgh, April 26, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 149)
    - Governor Thornburgh, First Informal News Session, Governor's Reception Room 9:30-10:30am, April 29, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 150)
    - Electronic Media Interviews, Harrisburg, April 29, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 151)
    - Jimmy Stewart, Recipient of the First Distinguished Pennsylvania Artist Award, Press Conference, Harrisburg [online], May 1, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 152)
    - Distinguished Pennsylvania Artist Award Ceremony, Harrisburg, May 1, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 153)
    - Dick Thornburgh Informal Newsroom Session, L Sides, May 6, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 154)
    - Interview, Harrisburg, May 6, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 155)
    - Speech at the Historical Preservation Conference, Camp Hill, May 9, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 156)
    - Informal Newsroom Session, Harrisburg, May 13, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 157)
    - Harvey Bartle III, Assistant Attorney General, Press Conference, Harrisburg, May 20, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 158)
    - Erie - Manufacturer's Association, May 21, 1980 (Box 1604, Cassette DTA 159)